在没有麦克风的介绍中，所以我们要开始
in the introduction without the microphone so we're gonna start going
microphone so we're gonna start going back to the liquor obligation as an
回到白酒义务为例，基本上看一下
back to the liquor obligation as an example basically to see how the
example basically to see how the equations look like for an undirected
方程看起来像是无向图，特别是对于摄影
equations look like for an undirected graph particularly for photography
graph particularly for photography okay so we're going to see how to delete
好吧，我们将要看看如何删除动物F的传播算法循环
okay so we're going to see how to delete propagation algorithm loops for animal F
propagation algorithm loops for animal F that has these cell potentials the way
就像您过去看到的那样具有这些电池的潜能，然后
that has these cell potentials the way you have seen in the past and then it
you have seen in the past and then it has this pair of potentials with receipt
在这里有收据这对电位，所以我们是节点数
has this pair of potentials with receipt here okay so we are the number of nodes
here okay so we are the number of nodes okay
好吧，让我们在图中的边缘，所以这个术语
okay SOT our edges in the graph so this term
SOT our edges in the graph so this term vs potential square potentials and Z is
与电位平方电位和Z是归一化因子没关系
vs potential square potentials and Z is the normalization factor all right so
the normalization factor all right so the the presentation it looks like a
该演示文稿看起来有点不同，但是您知道是否
the the presentation it looks like a slightly different but you know if you
slightly different but you know if you got the idea of message passing
有了有效传递消息的想法，它们是一样的东西
got the idea of message passing effectively they are the same things
effectively they are the same things okay so what we're gonna do is we are
好吧，我们要做的是基本上假设一个将军
okay so what we're gonna do is we are going to assume a general basically
going to assume a general basically Markov random field so and we're gonna
马尔可夫随机场，所以我们将使用与之相同的想法
Markov random field so and we're gonna use the same ideas we did for to it so
use the same ideas we did for to it so you know you can take the mountain from
你知道你可以把整个山都拿走，说你知道，并且
you know you can take the mountain from the whole thing and say you know and
the whole thing and say you know and whatever is from the bottom which are
不管是从底部到叶子都是什么，从某种意义上说都停止了
whatever is from the bottom which are the leaves and in some sense stop
the leaves and in some sense stop sending messages from the leaves to the
从叶子向根发送消息，这是收集证据步骤
sending messages from the leaves to the root that's the collect evidence step
root that's the collect evidence step and then going from the roots all the
然后从根源一直到链接，直到我们准备好
and then going from the roots all the way to the link before we are ready to
way to the link before we are ready to calculate marginal can do inference
计算边际可以做推断
所以因为我需要在信念传播这类概念中做到这一点
way to the link before we are ready to calculate marginal can do inference
so because I need to do this in the belief propagation sort of concept I'm
所以因为我需要在信念传播这类概念中做到这一点
belief propagation sort of concept I'm going to define what belief propagation
要定义什么是信念传播，所以我们做一个笔记-我的意思是一个笔记
going to define what belief propagation is so let's take a note - I mean a note
is so let's take a note - I mean a note P but just silver Nessun you even though
P但只是银色的Nessun，即使您不知道有向图
P but just silver Nessun you even though this to not you know a directed graph
this to not you know a directed graph but you can think of this if you found
但是如果您再次从T中找到它，您可以想到这些，这些是邻居
but you can think of this if you found it again from T these are the neighbors
it again from T these are the neighbors directly connected with lists of the of
直接与孩子的名单相关联，因此我们定义了
directly connected with lists of the of the children so we define that is called
the children so we define that is called the bottom half belief state of the node
在给定的情况下，节点T的下半部置信状态为XT的概率
the bottom half belief state of the node T to be the probability of XT given the
T to be the probability of XT given the evidence from below all right
好的证据，所以这个想法是，你会注意到
evidence from below all right so the idea is that you notice the
so the idea is that you notice the phrase the grafton this is the evidence
短语grafton这是来自右下方的证据，这是非常
phrase the grafton this is the evidence coming from below right this is very
coming from below right this is very important so this is what is called the
重要的是，这就是所谓的自下而上的信念状态
important so this is what is called the bottom-up belief state as you go from
bottom-up belief state as you go from the leaves to the rope to define the
绳子上的叶子来定义每个节点的置信状态
the leaves to the rope to define the belief state of every node and it
belief state of every node and it represents the probability of XT given
考虑到下面的证据，现在表示XT的概率
represents the probability of XT given the evidence below alright now the idea
the evidence below alright now the idea is somehow the way we have done in the
是我们过去所学的方法，我们已经学会了如何传播
is somehow the way we have done in the past we have learned how to propagate
past we have learned how to propagate vestiges from the tape from the timber
木材带子留下的痕迹很少，尤其是带电的
vestiges from the tape from the timber last few and especially as charged
last few and especially as charged right and so effectively this message
对，如此有效，您在此处看到的此消息是
right and so effectively this message that you see here is the probability of
that you see here is the probability of XT given this evidence and from the
XT给出了这些证据，从图表中您可以告诉我这些词是什么
XT given this evidence and from the graph can you tell me what the words
graph can you tell me what the words what evidence did I mean we did this in
我指的是什么意思，当我们与树木一起工作时，我们原则上做到了这一点，
what evidence did I mean we did this in principle when we work with trees and
principle when we work with trees and poly trees so this message is from s to
多边形树，所以该消息是从s到P的，实际上是P的概率，它
poly trees so this message is from s to P is really the probability of P and it
P is really the probability of P and it is this you know the belief basically
这是你知道的信念吗？
is this you know the belief basically given what evidence
given what evidence what do you think this evidence is it
您认为这个证据是什么，先说V下标s和T，然后-
what do you think this evidence is it says V subscript s and T and then - so
says V subscript s and T and then - so what's the idea here
如果我有优势，这里的想法是什么
what's the idea here if I have an edge
if I have an edge let this be a speed - is the evidence
让它成为一种速度-是来自图形的哪个部分的证据注释
let this be a speed - is the evidence comment from what part of the graph from
comment from what part of the graph from Mouse thing or plot gives noticed the
鼠标的东西或情节给人注意到了HST
Mouse thing or plot gives noticed the HST
HST you remember if you take espy right this
你还记得如果你采取间谍的态度，这就是子树，并且出现的证据
you remember if you take espy right this is subtree and the evidence of comes
is subtree and the evidence of comes from that it's really this message so
因此，这是真正的信息，所以这位大师总结了所有
from that it's really this message so this master summarizes all the
this master summarizes all the information the evidence that you see
信息，您在此蓝色海岸线下方看到的证据提供了
information the evidence that you see here below this blue coastline provides
here below this blue coastline provides you know T okay and so similarly to this
您知道吗，与此消息类似，我们也将消息发送给
you know T okay and so similarly to this message we also have the message to the
message we also have the message to the beauty etc so the bottom-up belief state
美女等，所以自上而下的信念状态T就是别的，
beauty etc so the bottom-up belief state of the know T it is nothing else but the
of the know T it is nothing else but the potential of the node X P times all the
节点XP的潜力乘以来自下面的所有消息
potential of the node X P times all the messages that are coming from below
messages that are coming from below alright so in this case two example this
好了，因此在这种情况下，这两个示例来自s和Q，因为该背心是
alright so in this case two example this graph from s and Q because this vest is
graph from s and Q because this vest is progressing you summarized all the
不断进步，您总结了我们自下而上获得的所有信念
progressing you summarized all the belief that we get from the bottom down
belief that we get from the bottom down okay so these are the children of T and
好的，所以这些是T的孩子，我再一次在宽泛的意义上使用它
okay so these are the children of T and again I'm using this in a liberal sense
again I'm using this in a liberal sense because this is not a directed graph
因为这不是我有孩子定义的有向图
because this is not a directed graph where I have a definition of children
where I have a definition of children but you can see what this implies from
但是您可以从该图中看到这意味着什么，因此我们传播消息并
but you can see what this implies from this graph so we propagate messages and
this graph so we propagate messages and the question is how do we compute this
问题是我们如何计算此消息以及如何计算此消息
the question is how do we compute this messages and we compute this messages
messages and we compute this messages recursively the way we have done before
递归的方式，我们以前做过的，但现在写的略
recursively the way we have done before but now this is written slightly
but now this is written slightly different so the message from below from
不同，因此从s到T的消息是从到的最大值s
different so the message from below from s to T it is a maximization s of the
s to T it is a maximization s of the joint potential of the non certainty
不确定性的共同潜能与我们之前所做的完全一样
joint potential of the non certainty exactly as we have done before
exactly as we have done before times the belief of first - the belief
乘以首先的信仰-不参加公共信仰的信仰，那是什么
times the belief of first - the belief of no - coming communal so what is
of no - coming communal so what is really the belief subscript s -
确实是信念下标s-的证据来自否
really the belief subscript s - is evidence of comes from the no
is evidence of comes from the no s-tronic service you can think of this
s-tronic服务，您可以想到这一点，例如，所有消息都是
s-tronic service you can think of this for example the all the message is
for example the all the message is coming to us from its children but now
从它的孩子那里来到我们这里，但是现在我写的是，因为
coming to us from its children but now what I have done is I've written because
what I have done is I've written because I define explicitly what this is for any
我现在明确地定义这是什么，我现在使用下面的信念
I define explicitly what this is for any now I am using the belief from below for
now I am using the belief from below for now to write this equation in a slightly
现在以稍微不同的方式写这个方程式
now to write this equation in a slightly different manner
different manner so actually spelling cannabis lists how
因此，实际上拼写大麻列出了事情的正确写法，但是如果您
so actually spelling cannabis lists how things were written right but if you
things were written right but if you don't like this definition you can go
不喜欢这个定义，你可以回到旧的方式，我的意思是
don't like this definition you can go back to the old way I mean the way with
back to the old way I mean the way with discussions with messages but in the
通过消息进行讨论，但是在信念传播的背景下
discussions with messages but in the context of belief propagation this
context of belief propagation this equation is written like a so if you
等式的写法是这样的，因此，如果您基本上是通过传播信念
equation is written like a so if you propagate beliefs basically from
propagate beliefs basically from evidence from below all the way to the
到达路线后，从下方一直到书面证据
evidence from below all the way to the written once you reach the route
written once you reach the route effectively you have the probability of
有效地，鉴于以下所有证据，您就有了路线的可能性
effectively you have the probability of the route given all the evidence below
the route given all the evidence below and effectively that according to our
实际上，根据我们的皮肤是北欧人的边缘
and effectively that according to our skin is the marginal of Nordics our
skin is the marginal of Nordics our times the product of all the messages
乘以来自根的子代的所有消息的乘积
times the product of all the messages coming from the children of the root to
coming from the children of the root to the okay but the messages are coming
可以，但是消息来自下面或人口基本上是
the okay but the messages are coming from below or population basically is
from below or population basically is the products of this normalization
该归一化因子CP和神秘Z的乘积变为ZT
the products of this normalization factor CP and the mystical Z becomes Z T
factor CP and the mystical Z becomes Z T basically is the normalization factor
基本上是下面每个信念阶段的归一化因子
basically is the normalization factor for each of this belief phase from below
for each of this belief phase from below you know what actually just produced
你知道在一行汇编中实际上产生了什么
you know what actually just produced upon one line compilation to convince
upon one line compilation to convince yourselves that it could take all of
自己可能会吸收所有这些味道，然后将它们相乘
yourselves that it could take all of this is a taste and you multiply them
this is a taste and you multiply them together from the leaves to the road you
从树叶到路，您基本上都会得到证据
together from the leaves to the road you basically get the evidence
basically get the evidence the Maserati could make a pelvic
玛莎拉蒂可以制造骨盆，还有一种额外的汽车炸弹
the Maserati could make a pelvic there's an extra sort of car bombs from
there's an extra sort of car bombs from this hopeless okay so here is and now
这是没有希望的，现在就可以开始分发了
this hopeless okay so here is and now you're ready to start distributing
you're ready to start distributing informational downwards to the same way
信息的向下传播与我们传递消息的方式相同，所以现在
informational downwards to the same way we have done with message passing so now
we have done with message passing so now as we start sending messages that say
当我们开始发送从T到s的消息时，我们将更新我们
as we start sending messages that say from T to s we are going to update us
from T to s we are going to update us then you notice now because when you
然后您会注意到，因为当您停止从T向s发送消息时，
then you notice now because when you stop message sending message from T to s
stop message sending message from T to s actually with no accessories which is
实际上没有附件，这就是在所有情况下都可以访问的可能性
actually with no accessories which is the probability of access given all the
the probability of access given all the evidence because we accounted evidence
证据，因为我们考虑了来自banila的证据和一些会计证据
evidence because we accounted evidence from banila and some accounting evidence
from banila and some accounting evidence from Abed all right so we the the belief
从阿贝德（Abed）好吧，所以我们认为X s的信念是给定V时X s的T，这是
from Abed all right so we the the belief of X s is T of X s given V and it is
of X s is T of X s given V and it is very simple is the belief you know it's
很简单的信念是，您知道这是自下而上的
very simple is the belief you know it's from the bottom up this is from the
from the bottom up this is from the first page of the algorithm finds all
该算法的第一页查找来自
first page of the algorithm finds all the messages that are coming from the
the messages that are coming from the parents but know this you agree in this
父母，但知道这一点，您同意在这种情况下Jaypee以及那里的其他东西
parents but know this you agree in this case the Jaypee and something else there
case the Jaypee and something else there okay so you know what we're doing
好吧，所以你知道我们在做大师的事情吗，我们有一些葱
okay so you know what we're doing masters passing we have some scallion
masters passing we have some scallion like they actually we're exactly how
就像他们实际上，我们正是这个方程看起来像之前
like they actually we're exactly how this equation on looking like before the
this equation on looking like before the messages when we didn't have this
消息，当我们没有这种信念的概念，那么很明显，我们有
messages when we didn't have this concept of belief so obviously we have
concept of belief so obviously we have the messages coming from above from the
从父母那里来的消息，在这里我们做到了，如果
the messages coming from above from the parents and here we did we have so if
parents and here we did we have so if you look at any node all right there's
您可以查看任何节点，不仅会收到来自团队的消息
you look at any node all right there's no not only receives messages from team
no not only receives messages from team but also receives message from what
而且还会收到来自
您必须现在包含所有消息中的所有消息
no not only receives messages from team but also receives message from what
you have to include the messages from the whole then of those messages now
您必须现在包含所有消息中的所有消息
the whole then of those messages now they're inside the belief - of now
他们在信念之内-现在可以使用一些牙膏了
they're inside the belief - of now effector some toothpaste the
effector some toothpaste the parameterization of the same Estes
同一Estes禁食的参数化会产生疑问
parameterization of the same Estes fasting a questions would have doubt
fasting a questions would have doubt there's really nothing you yep
你真的没什么
您知道我们的地理位置，因为我们赢得了我们的价格，我们通过了零售商，
fasting a questions would have doubt there's really nothing you yep
you know social location we win over the our price we passed the retailers and
您知道我们的地理位置，因为我们赢得了我们的价格，我们通过了零售商，
our price we passed the retailers and now we need to start replicating belief
现在我们需要从那里开始一直复制信念，因为
now we need to start replicating belief from there it all the way down because a
from there it all the way down because a lot of these notes have not yet received
这些笔记中有很多还没有得到进一步的信息，并且
lot of these notes have not yet received information from without going up and
information from without going up and down and actually you can do that the
下来，实际上您可以做到，唯一要做的就是您必须
down and actually you can do that the only thing you have to do is you have to
only thing you have to do is you have to initialize the message to be one so
将消息初始化为一个，以便有一些要发送的消息，然后
initialize the message to be one so there is something to send right and
there is something to send right and after that you don't really have to go
之后，您就不必真正上去了，而不必坚强地往下走
after that you don't really have to go up you don't have to go down strong this
up you don't have to go down strong this came out good
表现不错，这就是您所知道的
came out good and this is sort of what you know using
and this is sort of what you know using sort of an idea of listening
有点听的想法，你不能用消息来回应
sort of an idea of listening you can't respond same with messages
you can't respond same with messages anymore we can send messages send
现在我们可以发送消息了，可以发送消息了，但是现在我们是
anymore we can send messages send messages all right but right now we are
messages all right but right now we are looking for forward and backward
寻找向前和向后传播，我们用术语写
looking for forward and backward propagation and we writing this in terms
propagation and we writing this in terms of the list so the final belief of not
列表中的最后一个信念，因此不存在不存在的最终信念
of the list so the final belief of not exist having received information from
exist having received information from above and below is to believe that we
上面和下面是相信我们在从
above and below is to believe that we calculate this in as we went from the
calculate this in as we went from the links to the route and all the times all
链接到路线以及所有时间的消息的所有乘积
links to the route and all the times all the products of the messages that
the products of the messages that basically comes from the parlance of no
基本上来自不的说法，他们没事
basically comes from the parlance of no they're all right
they're all right and here's another equation now that the
这是另一个方程式，
and here's another equation now that the waves from the
从您已经看到的消息传递算法中，您可能会说，这是什么
from the message passing algorithm you have seen so you may say and what's the
have seen so you may say and what's the message that this sends to us now right
现在，当我们下山时，它立即发送给我们的消息从根部传到了
message that this sends to us now right as we go down goes from the root to the
as we go down goes from the root to the lives so that message is basically this
生活，所以消息基本上是这是定义权是
lives so that message is basically this is the definition right is the
is the definition right is the probability of XT given the upstream
XT的概率给出了T边上的上游证据，并且给出了
probability of XT given the upstream evidence on the edge of T and it's given
evidence on the edge of T and it's given by marginalizing so this is the
通过边缘化，所以这是要问正确的信息距离
by marginalizing so this is the information distance to ask right
information distance to ask right distance press does this look elect to
远距离新闻界这个词是否会让您感到紧张，所以看来我是
distance press does this look elect to you these term stress so it seems I am
you these term stress so it seems I am messed up the summation here okay so the
搞砸了总和好吧，所以信息Teamsters波峰将是
messed up the summation here okay so the information Teamsters crest will be the
information Teamsters crest will be the potential of the sphere and look at this
领域的潜力，现在就可以在许多情况下了解这一点
potential of the sphere and look at this now in many circumstances you know
now in many circumstances you know whether we have so if you look at the
如果您查看从T到s的消息，我们是否如此，所以您必须
whether we have so if you look at the message from T to s right so you have to
message from T to s right so you have to include the messages that arrived from
包括从上方传来的消息，请问我的功能好吗
include the messages that arrived from above to ask all right my function you
above to ask all right my function you have to include all the messages are
必须包括所有来自下面的消息，所以看看这个
have to include all the messages are coming from below so look at this
coming from below so look at this equation and tell me what exact is this
等式告诉我，这狗屎到底有什么确切的-在这个信念上，那又是什么
equation and tell me what exact is this  there's no - on this belief so what
there's no - on this belief so what exactly is this thing that we see this
正是这个东西，我们看到了这个分数
exactly is this thing that we see this fraction
我的意思是从重复中看到混乱时问我要走的愚蠢的水
I mean stupid water when looking the messes from repeat to ask okay going
messes from repeat to ask okay going downwards so what is this distance
向下，那么这个不相信状态的先生所穿的距离是多少？朱-
downwards so what is this distance dressed this misbelief state mr. Zhu -
dressed this misbelief state mr. Zhu - search maybe if you want addresses from
搜索，如果您想要上方和下方的地址
search maybe if you want addresses from above and below
above and below but here I'm dividing it by the message
但是在这里，我将其除以从下面发送提示的消息
but here I'm dividing it by the message that that sends the tip from below
that that sends the tip from below shall I stop you remember when you
我会阻止你的，记得当你更新的时候，我知道有消息
shall I stop you remember when you update right I know there's the message
update right I know there's the message coming from below and the message coming
从下面传来的信息，从上面传来的所有这些真的
coming from below and the message coming from above all of this really this
from above all of this really this message will give you the belief of
这则讯息会带给您北欧费的信念，但我将其除以
message will give you the belief of Nordics fee but I'm dividing it by the
Nordics fee but I'm dividing it by the message that essence today from below so
从下面传达今天的本质，那是什么，因为它们不会
message that essence today from below so what is that because they are not gonna
what is that because they are not gonna circular knowledge a mess is not an
混乱的知识是不可替代的
circular knowledge a mess is not an alternative
生活是一样的方式，记得我们不这样做的时候，所以这是早期的私有化
life is the same way remember when we don't so that's an early privatization
don't so that's an early privatization of the equations the way originally
方程式中最初引入信仰传播的方式
of the equations the way originally belief propagation was introduced in
belief propagation was introduced in principle really I mean if you correctly
原则上，我的意思是，如果您正确地通过两种方式都将得到相同的答案
principle really I mean if you correctly both ways you will get the same answer
both ways you will get the same answer so one way to look is this way another
因此，一种看待方式是另一种方式是通过消息传递传递为
so one way to look is this way another way is with a message passing passing as
way is with a message passing passing as we did before so it's the same story all
我们之前做过，所以现在是相同的故事，迁移和您做得很好
we did before so it's the same story all right now the migration and well you do
right now the migration and well you do this division as a song here is called
这种划分作为一首歌在这里被称为信仰更新俄语将是
this division as a song here is called belief updating the Russian will be
belief updating the Russian will be multiplied messages the way we have done
我们在前面的讲课中所做的事情是成倍增加的信息，实际上是
multiplied messages the way we have done in the earlier lectures is really the
in the earlier lectures is really the sum-product algorithm so that's what we
sum-product算法，这就是我们已经染过的东西，有了这个新的
sum-product algorithm so that's what we already have stained and with this new
already have stained and with this new parameterization you get this concept of
参数化，您会得到这种信念更新的概念，没有消息更新就可以了
parameterization you get this concept of belief updating no messages update okay
belief updating no messages update okay all right so this is it can happen that
好吧，这就是Southwick可能发生的情况
all right so this is it can happen that the Southwick
the Southwick you know you are operate on a tree the
你知道你在树上操作情况很简单，你知道
you know you are operate on a tree the situation is very simple you know if
situation is very simple you know if you're going to camp you know so let me
你要去扎营，你知道吗，所以让我看看这里
you're going to camp you know so let me look here it says
实际上让我让我，因为这是在早期的幻灯片中，所以我们正在寻找
actually let me let me because this was in earlier slides okay so we are looking
in earlier slides okay so we are looking now from the messages from top down all
现在从上到下的消息都可以从西边开始，好吧，所以我们只是
now from the messages from top down all right from feet west okay so we just
right from feet west okay so we just noticed equation okay and we sent the
注意到方程式还行，我们从西边的脚发送了消息，给出了
noticed equation okay and we sent the message from feet west is given with
message from feet west is given with these potential times the belief of node
这些潜在时间乘以节点XT的信念除以出现的消息
these potential times the belief of node X T divided by the message that comes
X T divided by the message that comes from below from load test so to update
从下面进行负载测试，因此要从上方更新此消息，您需要
from below from load test so to update this message this from above you need to
this message this from above you need to know investors coming from below so you
知道来自下方的投资者，所以您所需要的仅仅是保持
know investors coming from below so you need is not the sufficient to only keep
need is not the sufficient to only keep top of the beliefs of the nodes you need
您需要跟踪节点的信念，以跟踪即将到来的消息
top of the beliefs of the nodes you need to keep track of the messages coming
to keep track of the messages coming from below and that's why this message
从下面开始，这就是为什么如果您看到很多
from below and that's why this message is from above if you would see lots of
is from above if you would see lots of books interpret the test conditional
书籍解释了测试条件的后验概率，实际上
books interpret the test conditional posterior probability and actually in
posterior probability and actually in the slides that I gave you for directed
我给你的有向图幻灯片写的就像一个单元格
the slides that I gave you for directed graphs and written this is like a cell
graphs and written this is like a cell sample a posterior probability here is
在这里取样后验概率，您准备好考虑来自以下方面的证据了吗？
sample a posterior probability here is you are ready considering evidence from
you are ready considering evidence from below in computing these messages with
下面使用这种参数化来计算这些消息，以便您可以进行排序
below in computing these messages with this parametrization so you can put sort
this parametrization so you can put sort of the meaning of this being a
这是有条件的后验概率的意思，但是
of the meaning of this being a conditional posterior probability but
conditional posterior probability but the old way that we did right if you
如果您做不到的话，我们做对的旧方法就是
the old way that we did right if you cannot do that right so the
cannot do that right so the interpretation is basically these
解释基本上是这些信息就像可能性囊泡
interpretation is basically these messages are like likelihoods vesicle
messages are like likelihoods vesicle conditional likelihood
条件似然
我的意思是您可以看到例如这是为一块而写的，这里没有
messages are like likelihoods vesicle conditional likelihood
I mean you can see in for example this is written for a piece here there's no
我的意思是您可以看到例如这是为一块而写的，这里没有
is written for a piece here there's no message from below alright so you cannot
消息来自下面，所以您不能将其称为条件概率，因此
message from below alright so you cannot call it the conditional probability so
call it the conditional probability so the protocol basically in simple terms
该协议基本上是简单的术语，所以我们将向您解释
the protocol basically in simple terms right so we'll explain if you go from to
right so we'll explain if you go from to the list and then you can calculate any
列表，然后您就可以计算出任何种类的边际利益，
the list and then you can calculate any sort of marginal stuff of interest and
sort of marginal stuff of interest and you can calculate the dictates but
您可以计算命令，但实际上您可以做的是
you can calculate the dictates but actually what you can do is you can
actually what you can do is you can initialize all the messages to something
将所有消息初始化为某种东西，可以说是任意的
initialize all the messages to something and that can be arbitrary let's say
and that can be arbitrary let's say equal to 1 and it's really basically to
等于1，实际上基本上是从所有邻居那里接收消息
equal to 1 and it's really basically to take messages from all of its neighbors
take messages from all of its neighbors so you have they directly the belief of
因此，您可以让他们直接相信每个节点的电池势能时间
so you have they directly the belief of every node as the cell potential times
every node as the cell potential times the product of all the messages coming
来自所有邻居的所有消息的乘积
the product of all the messages coming from all of its neighbors
from all of its neighbors there's no anymore above and below you
上下再也没有了，您知道上游和下游的那种
there's no anymore above and below you know downstream and upstream sort of
know downstream and upstream sort of belief you can actually start updating
信念，您实际上可以通过这种方式开始更新所有节点的信念，并且
belief you can actually start updating the belief of all the nodes this way and
the belief of all the nodes this way and when are you going to convert when
基本上什么时候您打算何时转换
when are you going to convert when basically the message that you've
basically the message that you've converted and the message have converged
有效转换来自每个消息的信息时，消息已转换且消息已收敛
converted and the message have converged when effectively information from every
when effectively information from every other node so the number of steps
其他节点，因此基本上必须拖动此步骤
other node so the number of steps basically that you have to drag this
basically that you have to drag this would be as large as the size of your
会和图的大小一样大，所以它们基本上会收敛
would be as large as the size of your graph ok so so they basically converges
graph ok so so they basically converges linearly with the size of the graph
与图形的大小成线性关系，图形的大小与数量成正比
linearly with the size of the graph which is proportional to the number
which is proportional to the number in the gun right and if you check the
在枪的右边，如果您检查Nicollet，也可以找到
in the gun right and if you check the Nicollet sure that you will find too
Nicollet sure that you will find too much of different algorithms for doing
很多不同的算法来完成此确定，还有
much of different algorithms for doing finalization of this okay and there are
finalization of this okay and there are extremely fast
非常快，请记住，这一切都会开始
extremely fast and keep in mind this all gonna start
and keep in mind this all gonna start exactly
那里没有近似值的例子
exactly there's no approximation there example
there's no approximation there example okay so so they're very nice okay
好吧，所以他们很好，我想，所以他们给了你功课
okay so so they're very nice okay I think so they gave you homework you
I think so they gave you homework you know that if I remember if you're
知道，如果我记得您是否应该实施标记，那将是一种魔力
know that if I remember if you're supposed to implement a marker a magic
supposed to implement a marker a magic marker marker on appeal okay something
标记上的标记好吧，像这样的东西不完全是
marker marker on appeal okay something like that not exactly
它是无向块
it was undirected block
好吧，好吧，我没有怀疑是家庭作业3，如果我
okay okay I haven't questioned was homework 3 if I
I haven't questioned was homework 3 if I remember so here is a Gaussian Markov
请记住，这是一个高斯马尔可夫随机场，其中的单元势
remember so here is a Gaussian Markov random field where the cell potential
random field where the cell potential basically a Gaussian this is sort of a
基本上是高斯，这是一种归一化的高斯
basically a Gaussian this is sort of a normalized Gaussian
normalized Gaussian all right you close the square you get
好吧，当您关闭正方形后，您得到了高斯，然后您得到了他们的
all right you close the square you get the Gaussian and then you have their
the Gaussian and then you have their potentials to define Phi of s and T so
定义s和T的Phi的潜力，所以当您将所有这些放在一起时，
potentials to define Phi of s and T so when you put all of this together the
when you put all of this together the joint probability of X is really
X的联合概率真的是高斯，在这里我正在阅读
joint probability of X is really Gaussian and here I'm reading it I'm
Gaussian and here I'm reading it I'm writing it in sort of an immobilized
以固定下来的方式书写它可以，所以如果您感到极度恶心，
writing it in sort of an immobilized fall okay so the minima nausea if you
fall okay so the minima nausea if you close the square you're going to have to
关闭正方形，您将不得不将这个矩阵反转-1 B，然后
close the square you're going to have to invert this matrix a minus 1 B and this
invert this matrix a minus 1 B and this is a very costly calculation right
是一项非常昂贵的计算权重要指标，它进入了
is a very costly calculation right important metrics it goes to the cube of
important metrics it goes to the cube of the size of this matrix but if you do
该矩阵的大小，但是如果您使用此信念进行此计算
the size of this matrix but if you do this calculation using this belief
this calculation using this belief propagation now what it means you can do
现在传播意味着您可以做到的
propagation now what it means you can do it you have you with the size of the
it you have you with the size of the graph so we need to see how we can do
图，所以我们需要看看如何用高斯传播
graph so we need to see how we can do the propagation with Gaussian with
the propagation with Gaussian with Gaussian distribution so here is the
高斯分布，所以这是细胞电势的进步，但我
Gaussian distribution so here is the advance for the cell potential but I out
advance for the cell potential but I out here if you pull of the square
在这里，如果您拉平方，它是一个高斯，所以均值和
here if you pull of the square it is a Gaussian so the mean and the
it is a Gaussian so the mean and the precision are written here explicitly
精确地写在这里好吧，程序
precision are written here explicitly all right the the procedure the
all right the the procedure the marginals at every known country one
在每个已知国家/地区的边缘人都应该是高斯权利，因为您可以
marginals at every known country one should be Gaussian right because you can
should be Gaussian right because you can sleep on clearly if the joint is a
如果关节是高斯，就睡得很清楚
sleep on clearly if the joint is a Gaussian obviously all the margins will
Gaussian obviously all the margins will be Gaussian strong of interest will be
成为高斯人感兴趣的强项将是计算T和lambda T附近
be Gaussian strong of interest will be to calculate near T and lambda T okay
to calculate near T and lambda T okay and you need to do this at the cost that
并且您需要以与反转矩阵不同的代价来执行此操作
and you need to do this at the cost that is not the same as inverting that matrix
is not the same as inverting that matrix a but something way more efficient to be
但是需要一种更有效的方法来进行操作
a but something way more efficient to be able to do that we need to manipulate
able to do that we need to manipulate the audience and it sounds like a
听众，尤其是在一个维度上，这听起来像是对的
the audience and it sounds like a right when especially in one dimension
right when especially in one dimension but this can be very complicated if you
但这会非常复杂，如果您可以进行大量计算
but this can be very complicated if you can have an explosion of calculation
can have an explosion of calculation says especially if you try to explain
说尤其是如果您试图向您解释这一点，那么您只知道高斯人，但是
says especially if you try to explain this to you know just gaussians but
this to you know just gaussians but mixture of gaussians so what you need to
高斯混合体，所以您需要知道的一个简单的配方或药丸先生
mixture of gaussians so what you need to know sir one simple formula or pill one
know sir one simple formula or pill one is the format of gaussians and you have
是高斯格式，你必须写所谓的
is the format of gaussians and you have to write on what is called an
to write on what is called an information form share to use
信息表共享以使用Precision而不是非常坚持
information form share to use Precision's rather than very insist
Precision's rather than very insist divide this product in a nice form so if
将此产品以美观的形式划分，因此，如果您喜欢此产品，请优先购买第二级产品
divide this product in a nice form so if you like this with prestigious level two
you like this with prestigious level two one laughter - the product of two
一个笑声-两个高斯的乘积的精确度是
one laughter - the product of two gaussians has a precision which the sum
gaussians has a precision which the sum of the two Precision's and I mean that
这两个Precision的值，我的意思是这样给出归一化
of the two Precision's and I mean that is given like that the normalization
is given like that the normalization postulate is not important even like
即使这样，假设也并不重要
postulate is not important even like this
this I mean lot of the times right an
我的意思是很多时候对一个您知道不是的组织来说
I mean lot of the times right an organization you know it is of no
organization you know it is of no interest really you an interest rate so
利息的确是您的利率，所以我们需要做的是计算
interest really you an interest rate so that we need to do is we need to compute
that we need to do is we need to compute to be able to apply the different
以便能够应用其他评估权，因此，如果您查看
to be able to apply the different valuation right so if you look at the
valuation right so if you look at the belief of state note that first is the
相信国家，请注意，首先是访问的潜能乘以所有
belief of state note that first is the potential of access times all the
potential of access times all the messages arriving from its neighbors so
消息从其邻居到达，因此您需要能够在一个
messages arriving from its neighbors so you need to be able to compute this in a
you need to be able to compute this in a closed form as a Gaussian and then
封闭形式作为高斯，然后与该乘积一起是另一种形式
closed form as a Gaussian and then together with this product is another
together with this product is another closed out for Gaussian so you can write
为高斯而封闭，因此您可以写出没有多余的信念是愚蠢的
closed out for Gaussian so you can write the belief of no excess as a stupid
the belief of no excess as a stupid thousand and this is what this
千，这就是如果您编写
thousand and this is what this compression is done if you write the
compression is done if you write the messages to have a name USP and
名称为USP且精度为lambda的消息为3，然后乘以
messages to have a name USP and precision lambda is 3 and you multiply
precision lambda is 3 and you multiply all of this then you get a nice formula
所有这些，您就会得到一个很好的公式，可以相信您知道测试是
all of this then you get a nice formula for the belief of know the test to be
for the belief of know the test to be long passed right one pass I remind you
长传正确的一通我提醒您，这是因为它的精确性
long passed right one pass I remind you comes from the the precision of this
comes from the the precision of this single node potential plus the sum of
单节点电势加上所有质量的Precision的总和
single node potential plus the sum of the Precision's of all the masses
the Precision's of all the masses from the neighbors of s to militate okay
从s的邻国到好战好吧，所以非常好的12分钟一个大美元
from the neighbors of s to militate okay so the very nice 12 minutes a big dollar
so the very nice 12 minutes a big dollar must exist
必须一无所有存在，如果你不存在
must exist all right nothing and if you don't
all right nothing and if you don't update if you want to do message passing
如果要进行消息传递并且要从st p更新消息，请更新
update if you want to do message passing and you want update a message from st p
and you want update a message from st p you know this Bella right here
你知道这个贝拉在这里，我不认为事情是从上面来的
you know this Bella right here I don't assume things coming from above
I don't assume things coming from above and below because the idea is I am
以及下面的内容，因为我的想法是使用或初始化所有内容
and below because the idea is I am initializing everything with one or with
initializing everything with one or with some vouchers that you like and then I
您喜欢的一些优惠券，然后我会从每个音符中发出神秘的讯息
some vouchers that you like and then I mystic messages with every note from
mystic messages with every note from other neighbors so the metas promise to
其他邻居，因此metas承诺认为超出了
other neighbors so the metas promise to think much realized in excess of a
think much realized in excess of a mysterious in an integral form you have
具有不可或缺的神秘性，您有潜在的高级访问权限
mysterious in an integral form you have the senior potential access the
the senior potential access the potential of access honesty and then all
访问诚实性的潜力，然后是来自访问者的所有消息
potential of access honesty and then all the messages that arrive from the
the messages that arrive from the neighbors of the no vest except nullity
除了虚无以外，没有背心的邻居现在好了，我想通过
neighbors of the no vest except nullity okay now I want to go through the
okay now I want to go through the algebra but effectively we just have
代数，但实际上我们只是看到这是高斯式
algebra but effectively we just have seen that this are Gaussian this to a
seen that this are Gaussian this to a social Gaussian this was also Gaussian
社会高斯这也是高斯，那么有一个罪恶，所以
social Gaussian this was also Gaussian then there's a ssin in excess so
then there's a ssin in excess so technically at the end of the day you
从技术上讲，您可以在一天结束时得到一个递归方程
technically at the end of the day you can have a recursive equation that gives
can have a recursive equation that gives you this messages as a clothespin
您将此消息作为给定平均值的给定平均值的夹子高斯曲线
you this messages as a clothespin Gaussian with the given mean in a given
Gaussian with the given mean in a given procedure long term so effectively you
长期有效的程序，您会遇到scandi程序的问题
procedure long term so effectively you have this problem of scandi the program
have this problem of scandi the program to did the propagation called Gaussian
在鳍上进行了所谓的高斯市场的传播，这真的是你知道的
to did the propagation called Gaussian market on the fins it's really you know
market on the fins it's really you know the two lines
两行
没关系，您应该不要别人，您给了这项作业还可以，所以
market on the fins it's really you know the two lines
this is okay you should people not that you gave this homework okay all right so
没关系，您应该不要别人，您给了这项作业还可以，所以
you gave this homework okay all right so this is really all right now he realized
现在，这真的很不错，他意识到是可以解决的-好的，任何都可以
this is really all right now he realized yes to solve it - okay all right any
yes to solve it - okay all right any questions on this child now the only
现在，关于这个孩子的问题我唯一想说的就是
questions on this child now the only thing I want to say right when you look
thing I want to say right when you look at these formulas for the way
在这些公式中，约会消息的方式会有人留下，但是
at these formulas for the way dating messages somebody would stay but
dating messages somebody would stay but messages on a Gaussian right nothing is
高斯上的消息，没事，所以你要做很多
messages on a Gaussian right nothing is so you're going to do tons of
so you're going to do tons of nonparametric early and then the idea is
早期的非参数，然后的想法是我可以给你一个突发的高斯矩阵
nonparametric early and then the idea is can I give you a burst Gaussian matrix
can I give you a burst Gaussian matrix so you know what the problem will be
所以您知道当每条消息都是
so you know what the problem will be when every message everything is a
when every message everything is a Gaussian mixture what happens when you
高斯混合当您想将混合成分应用到
Gaussian mixture what happens when you want to apply a mixed in component with
want to apply a mixed in component with a lot of needs to go for it so multiply
为此需要很多工作，因此请乘以三部分，
a lot of needs to go for it so multiply you mix the three components with
you mix the three components with another mixtape let's ignacio components
另一个mixtape让我们ignacio组件您每30美元可获得多少组件
another mixtape let's ignacio components how many components you get $30 a
how many components you get $30 a mixture with a lot of three browsers
与许多三个浏览器混合在一起，您会得到九个然后是人类
mixture with a lot of three browsers what do you get nine and then humans
what do you get nine and then humans blind with another three all right
盲目与其他三个没事或北线，它继续前进
blind with another three all right or the Northern Line and it keeps going
or the Northern Line and it keeps going and going and so you get an explosion of
继续前进，因此您会爆炸成千上万个组件，通常
and going and so you get an explosion of thousand components so usually what
thousand components so usually what people do is they survive they take a
人们要做的是他们生存下来，他们混合了比遗传成分更多的东西，然后
people do is they survive they take a mixture than genetic component and then
mixture than genetic component and then they project it to a mixture with three
他们将其投影为具有三种成分的混合物，但同样，您也知道一些
they project it to a mixture with three components but again so you know some
components but again so you know some information okay and so the
信息还可以，所以即使尝试您的概率
information okay and so the probabilities even that try to you you
probabilities even that try to you you should for these five things don't
对于这五件事应该不会自动发生，但不一定
should for these five things don't automatically they are not necessarily
automatically they are not necessarily the exact right because you're gonna
确切的权利，因为如果您从九岁起就去听信息
the exact right because you're gonna listen information if you go from nine
listen information if you go from nine components two three you won't be able
组件二三，您将无法做到这一点，好吧，哥们
components two three you won't be able to do this exactly okay buddy has been
to do this exactly okay buddy has been that it has been not for many years
已经有很多年了，人们已经知道如何
that it has been not for many years almost 20 plus years people know how to
almost 20 plus years people know how to do this with Gaussian
用高斯做到这一点
好的
almost 20 plus years people know how to do this with Gaussian
all right
先生带有非参数置信传播名称的希格斯板
so mr. Higgs board with the name of nonparametric belief propagation
nonparametric belief propagation especially if you've used a mixed with
特别是如果您使用了非参数混合参数，那么您将知道
especially if you've used a mixed with nonparametric you know you're going to
nonparametric you know you're going to say I have a Gaussian mixture well but
说我很好地混合了高斯，但您知道您并没有承担任何高斯混合
say I have a Gaussian mixture well but you know you're not assuming any
you know you're not assuming any parametric form especially if the gods
参数形式，特别是如果众神混在一起，那么你可以有很多
parametric form especially if the gods are mixed you can there is many
are mixed you can there is many components as you wish right but also
您所希望的组件，但非参数组件也可能意味着分布
components as you wish right but also nonparametric can imply distributions
nonparametric can imply distributions that you represent agree with some hopes
你所代表的同意一些希望，我无法以一种非常好的方式
that you represent agree with some hopes well I cannot sort of a very nice way of
well I cannot sort of a very nice way of doing it message calculation so rather
进行消息计算，而不是尝试使其适合某些情况
doing it message calculation so rather than trying to fit them in some
than trying to fit them in some distribution for what you do is you
您所做的分配是用粒子表示它们，然后
distribution for what you do is you represent them with particles and then
represent them with particles and then when you calculate the message updates
当您计算消息更新时，您将计算新粒子
when you calculate the message updates you calculate the new particle
you calculate the new particle distribution to represent the questions
分布来表示问题好，那么实际上有什么技术
distribution to represent the questions okay so what's techniques actually have
okay so what's techniques actually have been extremely successful in in many
在很多方面都非常成功，我只能说大多数
been extremely successful in in many dimension and I would say most only they
dimension and I would say most only they are the state of the art for this type
是这种类型的计算的最新技术，也是另一种方法
are the state of the art for this type of calculation and another way to do
of calculation and another way to do this
这个非参数数组是给
this nonparametric array is to give
nonparametric array is to give additional approximation okay so you
额外的近似值还可以，所以您可以对分布进行疫苗接种
additional approximation okay so you vaccinate the distributions with some
vaccinate the distributions with some variation approximations and then the
变化近似，然后问题是如何计算这个新
variation approximations and then the question is how do you compute this new
question is how do you compute this new variation or approximation that's
变化或近似，我们将在稍后的内容中进行讨论。
variation or approximation that's something we will discuss later in the
something we will discuss later in the course we will spend maybe do a few
当然，我们将花费一些时间就该主题进行一些讲座
course we will spend maybe do a few lectures on the topic
顺便说一句，如果我短暂遇到的侦查问题，您会做
by the way if the scoutship problem that I briefly went through and you will do
I briefly went through and you will do it in the home or if your mobile is sort
它在家里，或者如果您的手机属于线性动力系统，
it in the home or if your mobile is sort of a linear dynamical system the
of a linear dynamical system the questions that you get with masters
大师通过等你遇到的问题实际上成为
questions that you get with masters passing etc become actually to be
passing etc become actually to be identical to thermal printer II so you
与热敏打印机II相同，因此您知道此消息传递算法将
identical to thermal printer II so you know this message passing algorithm will
know this message passing algorithm will give you exactly the same answers that
给您完全相同的答案，打印机将执行以下问题
give you exactly the same answers that come the printer does the questions will
come the printer does the questions will more complicated you know and
从概念上讲，您会更复杂，但实际上很多
more complicated you know and conceptually but actually much way much
conceptually but actually much way much much more elegant than the derivation of
比卡尔曼滤波方程的推导还优雅得多，所以
much more elegant than the derivation of the Kalman filter equations okay and so
the Kalman filter equations okay and so we will actually review and lots of
实际上，我们将回顾其中的许多内容，因为数据模拟是
we will actually review and lots of these things because data simulation is
these things because data simulation is important so I worship to get this
重要的是，我希望在我们经历这个过程时详细介绍这个概念
important so I worship to get this concept in detail as we go through the
concept in detail as we go through the course
当然可以，所以我们有25分钟的时间完成
course okay so we have 25 minutes to finish the
okay so we have 25 minutes to finish the junction 3 algorithm that we discussed
我们讨论过的路口3算法，基本上我不会做
junction 3 algorithm that we discussed and basically I'm not going to do
and basically I'm not going to do anything you know some very
任何你知道的阿尔伯特的参数化，然后
anything you know some very parameterization of the Albert and then
parameterization of the Albert and then one cute example of applying the
将联结树算法应用于隐藏的一个可爱示例
one cute example of applying the junction tree algorithm to the hidden
junction tree algorithm to the hidden Markov models and into the head of so if
马尔可夫模型一直以来都是如此，如果您从一开始就说
Markov models and into the head of so if you start let's say with a directed
you start let's say with a directed graph to get a junction tree the first
图以获取连接树首先，您需要做的是marelize
graph to get a junction tree the first thing you have to do is marelize and
thing you have to do is marelize and once you realize you replace all the
一旦意识到将所有有向边替换为无向边
once you realize you replace all the directed edges with undirected edges so
directed edges with undirected edges so here is organization making the path
这是组织制作路径Tektronix Plagne这条红线，这是
here is organization making the path Tektronix Plagne this red line this is
Tektronix Plagne this red line this is the factorization of the direction graph
方向图的因式分解，这就是它们从
the factorization of the direction graph and this is where they have from the
and this is where they have from the undirected graph so you can the color
无向图，因此您可以使用应该代表我们想要的颜色
undirected graph so you can the color supposed to represent we want one
supposed to represent we want one correspondence I mean really that's not
对应，我的意思是说这不是问题，但是这里的可能性是
correspondence I mean really that's not an issue but this probability here is
an issue but this probability here is nice high potential
很好的高潜力等
nice high potential etcetera etcetera
这是一个比较复杂的示例，例如出口历史记录星球
this is a bit more complicated example export history planet so basically have
export history planet so basically have to marry all of them straights not
嫁给他们所有的直道，不足以实际嫁给x2，而你
to marry all of them straights not sufficient to marry actually x2 and you
sufficient to marry actually x2 and you say x1 is the husband of you and excuse
说x1是你的丈夫，请原谅x1是汽车的极端医院
say x1 is the husband of you and excuse the hospital of extreme that x1 is a car
the hospital of extreme that x1 is a car politics the daily right no they have to
政治日常权利否，他们必须拥有个人证书
politics the daily right no they have to have an individual certificate of
have an individual certificate of marriage here so we need to connect x1
结婚在这里，所以我们需要连接x1 x3也可以，那么这就是
marriage here so we need to connect x1 x3 also okay then so this is how the
x3 also okay then so this is how the undirected graph will look like if you
如果您有证据要讨论此问题，则无向图将看起来像
undirected graph will look like if you have evidence we want to discuss this
have evidence we want to discuss this really there is nothing specific you
真的，您不需要做任何特定的事情，只需要切成薄片
really there is nothing specific you need to do but take slices of these
need to do but take slices of these potentials okay
通过固定到给定的值来确定潜在的可能性
potentials okay by fixing to the given values whatever
by fixing to the given values whatever known to travelers you have so in this
旅行者知道的，在这种情况下，给出的是4 X 3和X 4
known to travelers you have so in this case it's a 4 X 3 and X 4 are given
case it's a 4 X 3 and X 4 are given effectively you take a two-dimensional
实际上，您可以从一个二维切片中获取这一维
effectively you take a two-dimensional slice from let's say this one dimension
slice from let's say this one dimension table human dimensions lines etc and in
表人的尺寸线等，原则上平面节点在此
table human dimensions lines etc and in principle the plane nodes in this
principle the plane nodes in this problem become X 1 X 2 X 5 X 6 and
问题变成X 1 X 2 X 5 X 6和exedrin，从字面上您可以想到
problem become X 1 X 2 X 5 X 6 and excedrin and literally you can think of
excedrin and literally you can think of this equation X 1 X 2 I'll separate it
这个方程X 1 X 2我将它与X 5 X 6和X 7分开
this equation X 1 X 2 I'll separate it from X 5 X 6 and X 7
from X 5 X 6 and X 7 so maybe you can do this sort of
所以也许您可以在一个非常琐碎的事情中进行这种推论
so maybe you can do this sort of inference short opener in a very trivial
inference short opener in a very trivial manner you don't really have to mix
您实际上不需要将不依赖的事物混合在一起的方式
manner you don't really have to mix things together that don't depend on
things together that don't depend on each other the next step was to let me
彼此的下一步是让我看到已经写在这里的
each other the next step was to let me see this written here already for
see this written here already for buildin well so there was another
内建良好，所以下一个可能还会有另一个Stefan
buildin well so there was another Stefan's maybe going to come in the next
Stefan's maybe going to come in the next slide because it's not a problem on this
滑动，因为在此象形文字上没有问题，下一步是什么
slide because it's not a problem on this pictograph what was the other step that
pictograph what was the other step that was very essential
现代化之后非常重要，我们必须做什么
was very essential after modernization what do we have to
after modernization what do we have to do to create clicks that they are not
要做的是创建不属于您的点击，您知道它们不会导致您
do to create clicks that they are not you know they don't lead to you just
you know they don't lead to you just basically then was the best word we use
基本上，那是我们用来做连接树的最好的词
basically then was the best word we use to get a junction tree we have to do
to get a junction tree we have to do what to the graph so example let's say
该图的内容如何，​​因此示例可以在我的无向图中说，如果不是这样的话
what to the graph so example let's say in my undirected graph if this was not
in my undirected graph if this was not there when you're going to be happy if
如果今天不在那里，当你要快乐的时候，那是
there when you're going to be happy if you had today was not there that was
you had today was not there that was what is the step you have to do
在开始获得工作之前，您基本要做的步骤是什么
what is the step you have to do basically before you start getting you
basically before you start getting you know your junction tree yep
知道你的结树是
没有制图师博士。格拉夫把他们抛在我们后面
basically before you start getting you know your junction tree yep
no cartographer dr. Graf left them behind us
没有制图师博士。格拉夫把他们抛在我们后面
behind us what's the war I said not supplying us
我说没有在这里供应我们的战争是什么
what's the war I said not supplying us here
你知道其中之一，还有很多板块，还有可能性
you know one of them which was much more plates okay and the possibilities
plates okay and the possibilities basically as we wish I think in okay
基本上就像我们希望的那样
增加这个，我们必须满足一个基本属性才能做到这一点
plates okay and the possibilities basically as we wish I think in okay
increasing this this we have to satisfy a fundamental property to make this
增加这个，我们必须满足一个基本属性才能做到这一点
a fundamental property to make this problem consistent and we will discuss
问题是一致的，我们今天将通过示例进行讨论，那么什么是
problem consistent and we will discuss this with examples today so what was the
this with examples today so what was the exact property that we need to satisfy
我们需要满足的确切属性，才能使这种汽车用于农作物
exact property that we need to satisfy to make this sort of car to work crops
当我在这里查看这棵树时，我注意到第一个节点通过单击VD
when I look at this tree here I noticed this first node with a click a VD in
this first node with a click a VD in common so what did we say needs to
常见的，所以我们说在这个节点和那个节点之间需要发生什么
common so what did we say needs to happen in between this node and that
happen in between this node and that node if they serve no be the whoever of
如果它们不起作用，则结点树中任何不变的节点
node if they serve no be the whoever of no change in the junction tree to
no change in the junction tree to subscribe well you need to have what D
订阅得好，每当我收到信息时，都需要知道什么
subscribe well you need to have what D ok whenever I receive information going
ok whenever I receive information going to propagate
从这里传播到婴儿
to propagate from here to there to a baby it's going
from here to there to a baby it's going to mediate notes having no idea they
调解笔记不知道他们不在乎这个好吧，所以您需要
to mediate notes having no idea they don't care about this okay so you need
don't care about this okay so you need basically when you cancel you need to
基本上，当您取消时，您需要满足您所拥有的属性
basically when you cancel you need to satisfy that property of what you've
satisfy that property of what you've been taught now we actually reduce the
现在被教导了，我们实际上减少了分离主义者和
been taught now we actually reduce the concept of the separatist and the
concept of the separatist and the Cifaretto sphere are the squares
Cifaretto球是包含Kuna音符的方格知识
Cifaretto sphere are the squares knowledge that contain the Kuna notes
knowledge that contain the Kuna notes between the Terra Mystica VD and the
在Terra Mystica VD和再次单击之间，在这种情况下是
between the Terra Mystica VD and the click this again in this case are the
click this again in this case are the notes B and D and the converse operators
注意B和D以及相反的运算符，并且不要压迫它们会出来，或者
notes B and D and the converse operators and don't oppress them will come out or
and don't oppress them will come out or anything like that because clear every
那样的事情是因为清除包括分隔符主题在内的每个音符
anything like that because clear every note including the separator subjects
note including the separator subjects basically right I'm sorry mmm these are
基本上是正确的，对不起，这是这两次点击之间的共同定律
basically right I'm sorry mmm these are the common laws between those two clicks
the common laws between those two clicks but basically there is no factor so
但基本上没有任何因素，所以像我们这样做的事情
but basically there is no factor so anything like that the way we did in
anything like that the way we did in fact or not
事实与否现在可能说得很好，但如果是种族主义，那就是种族主义
fact or not now may say well but racist if it's a
now may say well but racist if it's a great comes with a potential right so
伟大带有潜在的权利，因此您可以思考代表
great comes with a potential right so that sense you can think representation
that sense you can think representation on the photograph but I'm not going to
在照片上，但我今天不打算使用这个概念，因为您知道
on the photograph but I'm not going to use the concept today because you know
use the concept today because you know the junction tree as a tree of with
结点树是带有白色节点的树，它立即带有
the junction tree as a tree of with white nodes immediately comes with its
white nodes immediately comes with its potential all right so these are the
可能没问题，所以这些是分隔符，然后，您知道
potential all right so these are the separators alright and then you know
separators alright and then you know basically let's say without discussing
基本上，我们先说一下，而不要讨论我们如何进行推理。
basically let's say without discussing about how we do inference right let's
about how we do inference right let's look at this know the conflict and this
看看这个知道的矛盾和这个便条，就是自己的便条熊
look at this know the conflict and this note that self notes beardy
note that self notes beardy what do you think the importance of the
您认为参数在这种情况下的重要性是什么
what do you think the importance of the parameter in this case what does it is
parameter in this case what does it is going to help us to remind us at least
至少可以帮助我们提醒我们走路，但是当蛇与人互动时
going to help us to remind us at least walk but when the snake interact what
walk but when the snake interact what Lincoln updates information of this
林肯会更新此点击的信息，反之亦然
Lincoln updates information of this click and the other way around
click and the other way around happens on what note
发生在什么音符上
也许唯一的记录表明他们是他们的故乡，所以这一次在其他时候
click and the other way around happens on what note
maybe the only notes that they're home to them so in other ways when this time
也许唯一的记录表明他们是他们的故乡，所以这一次在其他时候
to them so in other ways when this time okay a masters only we see whether it
好吧，只有主人，我们才能看到这是否意味着单击此电视。
okay a masters only we see whether it means to this click this TV is no
means to this click this TV is no medicine to mess about every because be
弄乱每件事的药，因为被搅动是不关心它有
medicine to mess about every because be stirred be doesn't care about it it has
stirred be doesn't care about it it has to be only on the notes that are in the
只能放在单独的音符上
to be only on the notes that are in the separate okay
separate okay and there is a mathematical issue that
我们需要在此处指定一个数学问题，我们将
and there is a mathematical issue that we need to specify here and we will
we need to specify here and we will citizen in examples right somehow
在示例中的公民以某种方式对我说的是生意，这是说一个
citizen in examples right somehow I mean business this is let say a
I mean business this is let say a believer countries on potential the
潜在的信徒国家逻辑上的信徒国家
believer countries on potential the separate on the logic on some potential
separate on the logic on some potential in a container you can guess maybe that
在一个容器中，您可能会猜测关于
in a container you can guess maybe that invisible jurisdiction with respect to
invisible jurisdiction with respect to any of the potential of the trickery be
骗局的任何潜力都将结束，我的意思是
any of the potential of the trickery be be finishing up I mean the potential of
be finishing up I mean the potential of the separator be they will be the
分隔符，因为它们将成为看见的边缘化，但是什么是
the separator be they will be the marginalization of the see but what is
marginalization of the see but what is the rational potential do not agree with
合理的潜力彼此不一致，这就是算法
the rational potential do not agree with each other that's what the algorithm
each other that's what the algorithm actually try to obtain but consistency
实际上试图获得但使两个组织平等的一致性
actually try to obtain but consistency that makes the two organizations equal
that makes the two organizations equal to each other
彼此之间，因此在某种意义上具有耗散性
to each other so in some sense having dissipators
so in some sense having dissipators that's what they will do so the sending
这就是他们将要执行的操作，因此发送消息基本上就是两次单击
that's what they will do so the sending message is basically this two clicks to
message is basically this two clicks to each other in a way that when given two
彼此的方式是，当给定两个盟友时，这与a和您有关
each other in a way that when given two allies this with respect to a and you
allies this with respect to a and you marginalize this with respect to see
边际化这一点，以了解如何以某种方式获得一致
marginalize this with respect to see somehow you can get a consistent
somehow you can get a consistent calculate
计算的分隔符应在
calculate of the separator for then shall be in
of the separator for then shall be in the process yes absolutely and this is
这个过程是绝对的，这就是我们今天要讨论的，是的，所以我们
the process yes absolutely and this is what we will discuss today yes so we
what we will discuss today yes so we think and then it was talking to rating
思考，然后在谈论评分，您给我发了一条消息，我给您发了一条
think and then it was talking to rating you sent me a message I sent you a
you sent me a message I sent you a message everybody sends messages to each
消息，每个人都互相发送消息，直到我们都高兴起来，好吧，所以
message everybody sends messages to each other until we're all happy okay so
other until we're all happy okay so where's my desk I told you way too much
我告诉你的桌子在哪里，太多的信息，让我们随着情节的来临
where's my desk I told you way too much information so let's as the plots come
information so let's as the plots come again we will see this again so we get
再次，我们将再次看到它，所以我们得到了主要的东西，然后这就是火车
again we will see this again so we get the main so then this is the Train on
the main so then this is the Train on directed and you can see the
指导，您可以看到三角剖分过程，所以我们
directed and you can see the triangulation process all right so we
triangulation process all right so we connected this block if the edges are
如果边是边，则连接此块，这是行程的定义，并且
connected this block if the edges are this is the definition of the trip and
this is the definition of the trip and effectively the message that I think we
实际上，我认为我们通过上一堂课的信息是
effectively the message that I think we passed last lecture was that so there
passed last lecture was that so there are many ways we can pose some what we
我们可以通过多种方式提出一些我们所说的内容，我们将选择一种
are many ways we can pose some what we said we are going to choose the one that
said we are going to choose the one that maximizes something and what is the many
最大化某些东西，应该使用哪些挑战？
maximizes something and what is the many challenges which one should be used so
challenges which one should be used so in this case we have this trade that has
在这种情况下，我们有两个独立的交易，每个交易有两个
in this case we have this trade that has two separate first each of them has two
two separate first each of them has two elements and then we have this 3 which
元素，然后我们得到这3分，即30分钟，他有一个元素
elements and then we have this 3 which is 30 minute and he has one element of
is 30 minute and he has one element of this separator and turned out whatever
这个分隔符，结果随你喜欢
this separator and turned out whatever you like
我们必须重新定义最大生成树，因为您知道我们将其称为
we have to redefine the maximum spanning tree with you know we will call it the
tree with you know we will call it the junction tree and when we say the
结点树，当我们说最大生成树的最大值为
junction tree and when we say the maximum spanning tree maximal with
maximum spanning tree maximal with respect to what he has too much my son
尊重他拥有太多我的儿子，所以如果你看这些日子，
respect to what he has too much my son tree so if you look at verse days what
tree so if you look at verse days what is the time between the two three
是两个三个之间的时间
好吧，答案是你必须看看分隔符
tree so if you look at verse days what is the time between the two three
well the answer is you have to look at the separator
好吧，答案是你必须看看分隔符
what is littering the separators invest twit P and in this the number of no all
乱丢垃圾的人投资了P，在这个数目中，没有全部
twit P and in this the number of no all right so here we have 2 + 10 + 2 + 2 is
对，所以这里我们有2 + 10 + 2 + 2大于1 + 2 3
right so here we have 2 + 10 + 2 + 2 is greater than 1 + 2 3 and these lots of
greater than 1 + 2 3 and these lots of heuristic algorithms on how to do this
关于如何执行此启发式算法的实际计算非常困难
heuristic algorithms on how to do this the actual calculation is a very hard
the actual calculation is a very hard one you know for a complex 3 but using
你知道一个复杂的3，但是使用经验方法可以很好地完成工作
one you know for a complex 3 but using the empirical methods give a job ok so
the empirical methods give a job ok so the natural trick has the largest total
在这种情况下，自然技巧具有最大的基数总分隔符
the natural trick has the largest total separator of cardinality in this case
separator of cardinality in this case for example you can notice here is the
例如，您可以注意到这里的基数仍然是10加2
for example you can notice here is the cardinality here is still so 10 plus 2
cardinality here is still so 10 plus 2 is greater than 1 plus I'm sorry 1 plus
大于1加上我很抱歉1加上2在行进的交叉路口还可以
is greater than 1 plus I'm sorry 1 plus plus 2 okay in the running intersection
plus 2 okay in the running intersection property is what we discussed before it
属性是我们之前讨论过的，您知道这个和这个之间的这个自我
property is what we discussed before it you know this self between this and this
you know this self between this and this next it has to be stare constant but any
接下来它必须保持凝视不变，但是在路径之间的任何其他单击都可以
next it has to be stare constant but any other click in between on the path okay
other click in between on the path okay so I just copy this 3 seconds before I
所以我只是在讲课开始前3秒钟就将其复制了，你知道我一直在
so I just copy this 3 seconds before I came from the lecture you know I always
came from the lecture you know I always try to find links for you to read more
尝试找到链接，以便您了解有关这些内容的更多信息，但不确定是否
try to find links for you to read more about these things right but not sure if
about these things right but not sure if you actually do but so stratosphere is
你实际上是这么做的，但是平流层是关于如何寻找的经验法则
you actually do but so stratosphere is an empirical law group on how to find
an empirical law group on how to find this maximal spanning tree and and the
这个最大的生成树和算法就在这个名字的下面
this maximal spanning tree and and the algorithm is just under the name of this
algorithm is just under the name of this crystal stir algorithm that is really
晶体搅拌算法，实际上是一种行之有效的启发式算法
crystal stir algorithm that is really sort of a heuristic algorithm that works
sort of a heuristic algorithm that works in not change not just for Junction
不仅改变结点树，而且在许多情况下也非常有用
in not change not just for Junction trees but this is very useful in many
trees but this is very useful in many other contexts as well so you know if
其他背景，所以你知道如果你击中这个，你会想到这个
other contexts as well so you know if you hit this you will come up to this
you hit this you will come up to this live animation and an example and region
实时动画以及问题的示例和区域，然后重新访问
live animation and an example and region of the problem now and revisit the
of the problem now and revisit the junction tree algorithm using the
结树算法使用分离的电位，所以我要
junction tree algorithm using the separated potentials so I'm going to
separated potentials so I'm going to cross paths with a parameterization that
交叉路径的参数化外观看起来像联合分布
cross paths with a parameterization that of the Joint Distribution that looks
of the Joint Distribution that looks like this relation that you see here
就像您在这里看到的这种关系是
like this relation that you see here that is the product of the potentials of
that is the product of the potentials of for the maximal cliques
对于我的联结树上的最大集团除以
for the maximal cliques on my junction tree divided by the
on my junction tree divided by the product of the potentials of the
分离器的电位乘积和概念上的乘积
product of the potentials of the separators and in conceptual and please
separators and in conceptual and please does this make sense right why you
这是否合理，为什么您会利用自己的潜力在这里发展
does this make sense right why you develop here by the potential of the
develop here by the potential of the separators
分隔符
看起来不是这样，我为您提供了一种预览方法来开始定义
develop here by the potential of the separators
doesn't look like this I gave you a preview way to start defining the
看起来不是这样，我为您提供了一种预览方法来开始定义
preview way to start defining the superlative the different one so these
最重要的是不同的东西，所以您可以从简单的东西中了解这些潜力
superlative the different one so these potentials you take know from the simple
potentials you take know from the simple interpretation equals one discussion
解释等于这里的讨论基本上第一运算符是一个
interpretation equals one discussion here basically first operators are one
here basically first operators are one and you can affiliate the connect
您可以将连接电位关联到您的原始非定向中
and you can affiliate the connect potentials in your original undirected
potentials in your original undirected graph with the clip potentials that you
图形，其中包含您在结3中使用的限幅电势，然后
graph with the clip potentials that you used in the junction 3 then the
used in the junction 3 then the numerator in that expression is actually
该表达式中的分子实际上是所有
numerator in that expression is actually the joint probability bution of all the
the joint probability bution of all the variables all right so mr. very general
变量好吗先生。如果您是我将使用的非常笼统的表达方式
variables all right so mr. very general expression I'm going to use if you are
expression I'm going to use if you are confused as to why is that consider that
关于为什么认为我从分母开始
confused as to why is that consider that I'm starting with the denominator to be
I'm starting with the denominator to be equal to answer there's no issue ok and
等于回答没有问题，然后我们会看到发生的事情
equal to answer there's no issue ok and then we would see what happens as we go
then we would see what happens as we go along okay you know the parameterization
好的，您知道我们在上一讲中讨论的参数化，但是
along okay you know the parameterization we discussed on the last lecture but the
we discussed on the last lecture but the equations are identical in other ways if
如果将两个x相邻放置，则等式在其他方面相同
equations are identical in other ways if you put the two x's next to each other
you put the two x's next to each other and you look at the equations they plan
然后看一下他们计划从中开始的方程式，但是随后您知道了
and you look at the equations they plan to start with but then you know with
to start with but then you know with some thinking they're identical so here
有些人认为它们是相同的，所以在这里我们到处都有分隔符
some thinking they're identical so here we have separator right everywhere okay
we have separator right everywhere okay we do not have this in the previous
我们在上一讲中没有这个，所以让我们开始
we do not have this in the previous lecture so let's so we're going to start
lecture so let's so we're going to start planting messages basically from the
基本上从链接中植入消息以进行更改
planting messages basically from the links to vary
links to vary to tell you the way we have done it in
告诉你我们过去的做法，所以让我们告诉消息
to tell you the way we have done it in the past and so let's tell the message
the past and so let's tell the message from a curriculum die to click no J did
从课程开始到没有J，我们都没有待最初的先生。政治的
from a curriculum die to click no J did we stay by the initial mr. political
we stay by the initial mr. political potential that no information no the
今天没有任何信息没有人的眼睛同意的潜力是关于哪一个没有
potential that no information no the eyes consent today is about which no so
eyes consent today is about which no so if I understand some information from
如果我从正确答案中了解了一些信息，如果您的信息
if I understand some information from right answer if your information a
right answer if your information a consent is the information related to an
同意是与更新的知识相关的信息，由以下人员共享
consent is the information related to an updated the knowledge that are shared by
updated the knowledge that are shared by CI n CJ I am going to send two giant
CI n CJ我将发送两个巨大的公司信息，有人知道该点击
CI n CJ I am going to send two giant firm ation what some knows this click
firm ation what some knows this click contains blood I'm not contain is to say
包含我不包含的血液，是因为那是你的任何人，所以不仅
contains blood I'm not contain is to say because that's your anyone so not only
because that's your anyone so not only are going to sent information that is
将要发送与当前变量相关的信息
are going to sent information that is related with the current variables
related with the current variables effectively what I need to do is the
我需要做的是有效地传达给我今天要传达的信息
effectively what I need to do is the message I'm gonna sell to my today will
message I'm gonna sell to my today will be the potential of you know I defined
是您知道的潜力吗？我通过NotI的轻拂定义了我整合的地方
be the potential of you know I defined by the flick of NotI where I integrate
by the flick of NotI where I integrate all the variables about the variables
有关分隔符中涉及的变量的所有变量
all the variables about the variables that are involved in the separator
因此我们发送了包含在此处的信息，但这指向本地
extent so we sent information contained here but this point to the local
here but this point to the local potentials for each of these nodes and
这些节点中每个节点的潜力以及您所知道的想法都已经过时了
potentials for each of these nodes and the ideas well you know take the old
the ideas well you know take the old potentials time if this is propagation
如果这是从节点列表中传播的时间，则时间为
potentials time if this is propagation from the list of nodes times are the
from the list of nodes times are the messages that are coming from the times
来自Pi时代的消息，我的意思是在一边
messages that are coming from the times of Pi I mean on the side
好吧，让我说这只是为了更新，好吧，你知道图片让我
well so let me say this just for update all right you know the picture let me
all right you know the picture let me see again
再看一次
所以查理，好吧，我没事吧，也许这
all right you know the picture let me see again
so this okay Charlie they things to I all right maybe this
所以查理，好吧，我没事吧，也许这
they things to I all right maybe this picture is know that proper to general
图片是知道适合一般约会的东西，实际上我知道你知道吗
picture is know that proper to general dating see I actually you know was it
dating see I actually you know was it thank you here actually thinking if it's
谢谢你，在这里，我在想这是否是因为我出差吓到了
thank you here actually thinking if it's because me from business out scare okay
because me from business out scare okay so basically all the messages of the
所以基本上所有的消息都是从没有男人的孩子那里传播来的
so basically all the messages of the propagated from the children of no guy
propagated from the children of no guy okay so basically you know I had one
好的，所以基本上您知道我有一个图形，他们必须使用它才能使用
okay so basically you know I had one graphing they have to use it you can use
graphing they have to use it you can use the industries and give them the right
行业，并为他们提供对您想要的方式的正确解释
the industries and give them the right interpretation of the way you wanted a
interpretation of the way you wanted a physical IJ and because mister natality
身体上的IJ，并且因为先生的出生天分处理了我们需要做的是
physical IJ and because mister natality processed what we need to do is we need
processed what we need to do is we need to update the messages without basically
在基本上不分离潜在问题的情况下更新消息，因此请看
to update the messages without basically separate the potential okay and so look
separate the potential okay and so look at this equation carefully and and
在这个方程式上仔细地尝试并尝试赋予一些个人意义
at this equation carefully and and trying to give some personal meaning to
trying to give some personal meaning to what it takes
需要什么
所以这是一种定义权，但是您可以认为这是
trying to give some personal meaning to what it takes
so this is sort of a definition right but this you can think of this being the
所以这是一种定义权，但是您可以认为这是
but this you can think of this being the amazing potential of the separator s9j
分离器s9j的惊人潜力
所以这个等式说了今天来自Lodi的其他关于斋戒的信息
but this you can think of this being the amazing potential of the separator s9j
so what this equation says the other information of the fast from Lodi today
所以这个等式说了今天来自Lodi的其他关于斋戒的信息
information of the fast from Lodi today we have to integrate over modernist
我们必须整合现代主义者，除了那些包含一个单独的他们
we have to integrate over modernist except the ones contain a separate them
except the ones contain a separate them but the notice here there's a division
但是这里的通知有一个惊喜
but the notice here there's a division from surprise
再次与您的概念有关
and again this is related to what your concept
我要用精确的计算说服您，为什么这行得通，但是
I'm gonna convince you with a precise calculation why this works right but
calculation why this works right but shared this division is very similar to
共享此部门与具有信念的部门非常相似
shared this division is very similar to the division who has the belief
the division who has the belief propagation algorithm respectively why
传播算法分别为什么在分母中有这个
propagation algorithm respectively why do we have this in the denominator
你没有告诉英联邦我从杰克那里得到的信息，我们没人怀疑
you didn't tell Commonwealth my message from Jake are we no one can doubt
from Jake are we no one can doubt melancholy the message that basically
忧郁的信息，基本上是野牛链的味道，所以这
melancholy the message that basically the Bison taste of chains so this
the Bison taste of chains so this calculation
计算
好吧好吧好吧
the Bison taste of chains so this calculation
okay okay all right
一切都从非常可接受的学期项目开始，所以我要几天
everything from very acceptable semester project so then I'm gonna days once I
project so then I'm gonna days once I have updated this operator potential I
已经更新了此操作员的潜力，我将更新
have updated this operator potential I am going to update the potential of the
am going to update the potential of the Qaddafi and the real dated is the old
卡扎菲和真正的过时是触发W的旧势乘以减弱的势
Qaddafi and the real dated is the old potential of trig W times the abated
potential of trig W times the abated separated people potential divided by
分离的人的势力除以原始的分离的势力还可以
separated people potential divided by the original separated potential okay
the original separated potential okay that sounds good
听起来不错，我们将展示正确的内容
that sounds good we will show right what obviously
we will show right what obviously passing messages can wait to battle you
传递消息可能会等您打架，因此，如果没有办法
passing messages can wait to battle you so the potential if there's no way to
so the potential if there's no way to change to another man exactly so let's
换个男人，让我们看看我们该如何将那些墨西哥人
change to another man exactly so let's see how we're gonna send those Mexican
see how we're gonna send those Mexican value T to V so we're gonna have to
值T到V，所以我们将不得不更新分隔器的电势
value T to V so we're gonna have to update the potential of the separator
update the potential of the separator how do we do this by taking the
我们如何通过记住W是更新的W的潜力来做到这一点
how do we do this by taking the potential of W which remember was update
potential of W which remember was update me to this and we're going to integrate
我要注意这一点，我们将把所有的维生素缓冲剂整合到
me to this and we're going to integrate all the vitamins buffers in the
all the vitamins buffers in the separator and then we are going to
分离器，然后我们将更新V的电势，请记住
separator and then we are going to update the potential of V which remember
update the potential of V which remember was this and how we're going to update
是这个，我们将如何更新，可能存在分隔符
was this and how we're going to update there may be potential of the separator
there may be potential of the separator divided by the previous value of the
除以分隔器电位的先前值乘以try
divided by the previous value of the potential of the separators times try
potential of the separators times try the star which is this and the potential
这颗恒星和Gavi的潜力将保持更新，以开始
the star which is this and the potential of Gavi will remain the updated to start
of Gavi will remain the updated to start swimming with what it was before so
和以前一样游泳，所以从V到W的消息正在更新
swimming with what it was before so messages from V to W and I'm updating
messages from V to W and I'm updating the separator potential the davia
分隔器电位davia电位V电位实际上不是
the separator potential the davia potential the V potential really doesn't
potential the V potential really doesn't change and then messages from EE here to
更改，然后从EE这里发给我的消息
change and then messages from EE here to me
me I am updating the separation it separate
我正在更新间隔，它将电位V和电位V分开。
I am updating the separation it separate the potential the potential of V and the
the potential the potential of V and the potential now he doesn't say why this
潜力，现在他没有说这为什么最有效-那些属于问
potential now he doesn't say why this works most - those that belong in ask so
works most - those that belong in ask so well so this is probably double stars
好吧，这可能是双星尝试吃植物吧，这是这个
well so this is probably double stars try plant-eating right this is this this
try plant-eating right this is this this comes outside the summation sign
在求和标志西班牙裔IV之外，这是什么pH值
comes outside the summation sign hispanist IV and what is this this is pH
hispanist IV and what is this this is pH are you still at the discount of tau
您是否仍在以tau的价格打折，这是下半部的长度
are you still at the discount of tau this is the second half length of the
this is the second half length of the separator potential which is what is the
分隔电位是所有节点的总和，但从
separator potential which is what is the summation of all the nodes but as from
summation of all the nodes but as from darling you
亲爱的你
[掌声]
summation of all the nodes but as from darling you
[Applause]
分隔符的潜力是相同的，无论我是否完成了
the potential of the separator is the same regardless my completed my
same regardless my completed my marginalization of the potential on the
左边的潜力或整体潜力的边际化
marginalization of the potential on the left or the potential overall so
left or the potential overall so basically by you can think of this you
基本上，您可以想到的是，您知道前锋和一团糟的恶心
basically by you can think of this you know a forward and a mess disgusting I
know a forward and a mess disgusting I have achieved basically with some
基本上取得了一些一致性，这正是我的工作
have achieved basically with some consistency which is exactly what I work
基于论文，这种潜力之间的一致性是由
is based on the papers this consistency between the potentials defined by the
between the potentials defined by the clicks if you don't have this sort of
如果您没有这种明确的点击，您仍会以某种方式知道
clicks if you don't have this sort of explicitly you know somehow still you
explicitly you know somehow still you will need to satisfy some consistency
将需要满足一些一致性关系，但是在这里它们有点
will need to satisfy some consistency relations but here they are sort of
relations but here they are sort of straightforward basically for the
基本上对于上一张图片而言，本幻灯片是简单明了的，因为
straightforward basically for the previous picture this the slide because
previous picture this the slide because I'm not going to repeat them again the
我不再重复它们了
您不能说您是从这里发送消息的，所以我们必须更新
previous picture this the slide because I'm not going to repeat them again the
you cannot say you sent messages from here to there so we have to update
您不能说您是从这里发送消息的，所以我们必须更新
here to there so we have to update basically the potential of the separator
基本上是分离器的潜力，这就是我们要做的，然后，我们必须
basically the potential of the separator this is what we did then we have to
this is what we did then we have to update the potential of this click by
通过乘以之前的值来更新此点击的可能性
update the potential of this click by multiplying the previous values of the
multiplying the previous values of the potential with size start dividing
规模的潜力开始分裂生活方式，您还记得我们从
potential with size start dividing lifestyle and you remember we start with
lifestyle and you remember we start with the separator potential to be equal to 1
分隔器电位等于1，然后做标记
the separator potential to be equal to 1 and then we do the markers
and then we do the markers so he marginalised say I start for
所以他被边缘化了，说除了先生，我开始一切。佩雷（Perret）最能体现
so he marginalised say I start for everything except mr. Perret embody most
everything except mr. Perret embody most and then you have take as we spend Isis
然后您花了我们Isis提供的费用入狱，从而更新了潜在的
and then you have take as we spend Isis provide to jail you update the potential
provide to jail you update the potential of J this factor and at the end of the
J的这个因素，并在一天结束时，如果您实际上保持一致，以及何时
of J this factor and at the end of the day if you actually consistency and when
day if you actually consistency and when you know doing all of these calculations
你知道所有这些计算都是边际分布，你知道
you know doing all of these calculations the marginal distribution and you know
the marginal distribution and you know the variables remains unchanged okay and
变量保持不变好吧，我认为幻灯片中有一些内容
the variables remains unchanged okay and I think there is some put in the slides
I think there is some put in the slides that shows that but basically very we
这表明，但基本上，我们不参与联合概率
that shows that but basically very we don't play with the joint probability
don't play with the joint probability distribution with all these local
分发所有这些本地更新，因为本地更新
distribution with all these local updates because the local updates
updates because the local updates maintain the joyful of in distribution
在迭代过程中保持快乐的分布是相同的
maintain the joyful of in distribution to be to be the same during iterations
to be to be the same during iterations and actually chemists you know I am I
实际上，化学家，你知道我是我，我只是用一个微不足道的例子说
and actually chemists you know I am I just said with the trivial example that
just said with the trivial example that perfect does not change basically in
完美在根本上既不会改变，也不会改变
perfect does not change basically in either the forward of the backwards that
either the forward of the backwards that it remains the same okay I have 30
仍然一样，我有30分钟，我将做一个例子
it remains the same okay I have 30 minutes and I'm going to do one example
minutes and I'm going to do one example the struggles it sounds like another
听起来像是另一场被杀的斗争，但我想向你展示
the struggles it sounds like another killed right but I wanted to show you
killed right but I wanted to show you how you can actually apply this to real
如何将其实际应用于实际问题，这就是凝聚力马尔可夫
how you can actually apply this to real problems so this is cohesion Markov
problems so this is cohesion Markov models that I will start discussing
我将在周四开始讨论细节的模型，但我们将要做
models that I will start discussing detail on Thursday but we're going to do
detail on Thursday but we're going to do the junction tree algorithm with the
今日hmm模型的带有分隔符的结点树算法
the junction tree algorithm with the separators for the hmm model today
对于那些还没有看过嗯LD的人-我们可以做一些糖动力学吗？
for those who have not seen it the hmm LD - can we have some sugar dynamics so
LD - can we have some sugar dynamics so there's notes that the shielded waffle
需要注意的是，屏蔽华夫饼是随着
there's notes that the shielded waffle is the system state that evolves with
is the system state that evolves with some dynamics and right now we assumed
一些动态，现在我们假设现代智能为贝因，所以
some dynamics and right now we assumed that the modern smart for bein so the
that the modern smart for bein so the probability of being on a given state
处于给定状态的概率仅取决于您所处的状态
probability of being on a given state here depends only on the state that you
here depends only on the state that you were before and it's defined by this
之前，它是由这种过渡定义的，您说嘿，以某种方式
were before and it's defined by this transition that you say hey and somehow
transition that you say hey and somehow you want to infer this hidden states by
您想通过我自愿进行的一些大观察来推断这种隐藏状态
you want to infer this hidden states by some large observations that I volunteer
some large observations that I volunteer y0 y1 white the white pocket empty or
y0 y1白色白色的口袋里空的或类似的东西，所以我们想做
y0 y1 white the white pocket empty or something like that so we want to do
something like that so we want to do sort of the junction 3 algorithm and in
交界处3算法的种类，在此过程中，您可以发现
sort of the junction 3 algorithm and in the process you can discover the
the process you can discover the probabilistic after matters all the
事后概率，您知道的所有方程式您可能都不知道
probabilistic after matters all the equations from you know you may not know
equations from you know you may not know about Kalman filtering in a show you can
关于节目中的卡尔曼滤波，您可以派生任何形式的扩展来
about Kalman filtering in a show you can derive any sort of extensions to come a
derive any sort of extensions to come a filtering your interest rate for the
使用治愈方法为穿梭机过滤您的利率，但是
filtering your interest rate for the shuttle distribution I using a cure but
shuttle distribution I using a cure but somehow I have to change the slides so
我必须以某种方式更改幻灯片，以使这种奇偶性吓到了Y的持续时间，因此
somehow I have to change the slides so this parity scare the durations of Y so
this parity scare the durations of Y so the joint of a minute radiation of Q and
Q和y的微小辐射的联合是由
the joint of a minute radiation of Q and y is given by the probability of the
y is given by the probability of the initial stage which is the transition
初始阶段是从-t2 t2加1到
initial stage which is the transition probabilities from - t2 t2 plus 1 and
probabilities from - t2 t2 plus 1 and this is the observation model many most
这是许多人最希望的观察模型
this is the observation model many most probably hoped
probably hoped without right some sort of just a little
没有权利，只是一点点没事，所以我再次希望你
without right some sort of just a little bit all right so again I want you as an
bit all right so again I want you as an overkill application right because you
过度杀害应用程序的权利，因为您不能应用非常重要的内容
overkill application right because you can't apply something that is very
can't apply something that is very general a trivial problem
一般的小问题，我们知道答案听起来像
general a trivial problem we know the answer they sound like
we know the answer they sound like another kid but it's a very good
另一个孩子，但这是一个非常好的
职位分布中的职业道德AI J
we know the answer they sound like another kid but it's a very good
position ethics AI J the in the join distribution
职位分布中的职业道德AI J
ethics AI J the in the join distribution here right I can write it's playable
在这里我可以写它是可玩的这是QT加1的概率
here right I can write it's playable this is the probability of QT plus 1
this is the probability of QT plus 1 given Q T so we find all the metrics say
给定QT，因此我们发现所有指标都说明了我非常定义的
given Q T so we find all the metrics say which components a I'm very defined the
which components a I'm very defined the way is secure so I go from state I time
方法是安全的，所以我从状态I到时间T，您知道状态J在T加上1 I
way is secure so I go from state I time step T you know state J on T plus 1 I
step T you know state J on T plus 1 I can write this as a IJ 250 I 50 plus 1 J
可以写成IJ 250 I 50 plus 1 J从，我假设我有一个
can write this as a IJ 250 I 50 plus 1 J from and I'm assuming here I have a
from and I'm assuming here I have a multinomial distribution so the values
多项式分布，因此状态的值可以是n个不同的值
multinomial distribution so the values of the states can be n different values
of the states can be n different values of its time then you should ask I mean
那时候，你应该问我的意思是，这不是三眼神，除非你知道
of its time then you should ask I mean isn't this triply eyes except you know
isn't this triply eyes except you know some of them would be 1 and that's what
其中一些会是1，这就是我们想要的，他们会给您正确的
some of them would be 1 and that's what we want they will give you the correct
we want they will give you the correct element for my transition matrix AI J
我的过渡矩阵AI J的元素没有更快的方式了
element for my transition matrix AI J there's nothing faster okay again the
there's nothing faster okay again the for identification state to ask this
识别状态从
for identification state to ask this transition probabilities from the
transition probabilities from the dynamics and times of the vegetable so
蔬菜的动态和时间，所以当我们做一个状态空间
dynamics and times of the vegetable so the when we do states a state-space
the when we do states a state-space models in the next week or so the
下一周左右的模型在上下文中的基本问题
models in the next week or so the fundamental problems in the context of
fundamental problems in the context of data simulation is basically if you're
基本上，如果没有给出数据模拟，则不要定义P来估计
data simulation is basically if you're given don't define P to estimate the
given don't define P to estimate the state of time T that's what is called
时间状态T即所谓的烧结问题预测
state of time T that's what is called the sintering problem the prediction
the sintering problem the prediction problem is if you are given data up to
问题是，是否给您提供了有关习惯预测的数据，
problem is if you are given data up to time s to the predictions of habit
time s to the predictions of habit raishin but the prediction problem and
葡萄干，但预测问题，然后是锻造问题是，如果你是
raishin but the prediction problem and then the smithing problem is if you are
then the smithing problem is if you are given observations from now on till
从现在到明天给出的观察结果，我们可以预测分布
given observations from now on till tomorrow can we predict distributing
tomorrow can we predict distributing what the state is so here using a lot of
使用大量数据（包括未来数据）来预测这里的状态是什么
what the state is so here using a lot of data including future data to predict
data including future data to predict the state of the given value time and
给定值时间的状态，显然没有任何假设，因为
the state of the given value time and suppose nothing obviously because this
suppose nothing obviously because this would be very smooth to answer than what
答案将比使用各种打印机得到的答案要平滑得多
would be very smooth to answer than what you would get with printer various
you would get with printer various problems you can address them with
您可以通过概率图形模型解决这些问题
problems you can address them with probabilistic graphical models and
probabilistic graphical models and actually we talked on deeper messages
实际上，我们讨论了更深层的信息，我们为改变所做的事情，但是我
actually we talked on deeper messages the way we did for for changed but I
the way we did for for changed but I will again do another King today to use
今天将再次做另一位国王使用结点树来显示这一点
will again do another King today to use the junction tree over to show this
the junction tree over to show this problem okay just think you can get the
问题好吧，只要以结点树为思路，就认为您可以得到Peconic
problem okay just think you can get the Peconic if the junction tree thinking
Peconic if the junction tree thinking deeply so children for example to
如此深的儿童例如计算
deeply so children for example to calculate the marginal of the
calculate the marginal of the observations you can see the summation
观察结果，您可以在这里看到这一挑战的总和，因为如果您有
observations you can see the summation here this challenge because if you have
here this challenge because if you have these steps and each day but you have to
这些步骤以及每一天，但是您必须要取一些值，这就是M
these steps and each day but you have to some take some values this is M to the
some take some values this is M to the time m to Capitol Hill calculations so
时间到国会山的时间，所以这是非常昂贵的，我们需要
time m to Capitol Hill calculations so this is very expensive we need to be
this is very expensive we need to be able to do this table for problems with
能够解决此问题的表格远胜于此指数课程
able to do this table for problems with well better than this exponential course
我认为我将无法继续实现它，但让我们尝试做一下
I don't think I would be able to proceed um realizing it but let's try to do our
um realizing it but let's try to do our best so if you reminders of some of the
最好，因此，如果您提醒一些开始的事情，我们会来的，
best so if you reminders of some of the things beginning we will come and
things beginning we will come and discuss them slowly in front of lectures
在讲座前慢慢讨论它们，但如果您在这里看到，我想使用
discuss them slowly in front of lectures but I want to use okay if you see here
but I want to use okay if you see here is the smoothing problem I am well aware
是平滑的问题，我很清楚这些导数，因为我没有
is the smoothing problem I am well aware of the derivations because I don't have
of the derivations because I don't have the time and since we will repeat this
时间，既然我们将重复这项权利，那么我只想说一句
the time and since we will repeat this right let me just say that by using this
right let me just say that by using this basic probability was a no-show
基本概率是通过使用条件独立性而没有出现
basic probability was a no-show by using conditional independence
by using conditional independence relationships applied by this graph
该图所应用的关系基本上是给定节点的关系
relationships applied by this graph basically that which are given the node
basically that which are given the node P P Q P plus 1 is independent of QT
PPQP加1独立于QT减1，独立于类型
P P Q P plus 1 is independent of QT minus 1 right the type of Independence
minus 1 right the type of Independence relations you can show that this moving
关系可以表明，这种移动概率实际上是
relations you can show that this moving probability it's really the product of
probability it's really the product of the non semesters which is absolute
非学期，即绝对学期x 2 bar减去beta除以P
the non semesters which is absolute masters x 2 bar minus beta divided by P
masters x 2 bar minus beta divided by P of Y the marginal of Y and the
Y的Y的边际和alpha方法的定义是这个
of Y the marginal of Y and the definition of the alpha methods is this
definition of the alpha methods is this entity here and the definition of the
实体，如果您在此处仅显示元消息的定义，
entity here and the definition of the meta message just presented there if you
meta message just presented there if you look at this definition that comes
看一下这个定义，基本上来做推导非常
look at this definition that comes basically do the derivation is very
basically do the derivation is very simple is that is the probability that
简单的是，您将观察到y0 y1 y3然后在
simple is that is the probability that you will observe y0 y1 y3 and then in
you will observe y0 y1 y3 and then in the end of stage GT all right
GT阶段结束了，所以alpha只是
the end of stage GT all right so alpha is merely something that
so alpha is merely something that accounts for all your observations of
解释了您对阻止电视进行的前瞻性计算的所有观察结果
accounts for all your observations of deterring TV sort of forward calculation
deterring TV sort of forward calculation but the trace is the joint probability
但是痕迹是
but the trace is the joint probability of
the observed date of to little T assuming that you've finished in state
假设您已经完成状态，则观测到的小T的日期
assuming that you've finished in state 50 and you can show the first message is
50，您可以看到第一个消息是您必须计算
50 and you can show the first message is that you have to calculate this
that you have to calculate this probability and this really can be
概率，而这确实可以递归计算
probability and this really can be calculated recursively we have been
calculated recursively we have been encouraged to the questions for the
鼓励回答有关Alpha方法和递归方程的问题
encouraged to the questions for the Alpha method and the recursive equation
Alpha method and the recursive equation for the beta message noticed that the
对于beta消息，请注意Alpha消息的更新是
for the beta message noticed that the updating of the Alpha message is
updating of the Alpha message is affirmative date so we reverse the
确定日期，因此我们将消息Alpha QT和观察结果反转了
affirmative date so we reverse the message alpha Q T and the observation
message alpha Q T and the observation model of the dynamics to update so there
动态模型以进行更新，因此如果您采取此方法，则将被边缘化
model of the dynamics to update so there is a marginalization if you take here
is a marginalization if you take here and the bigger message is the bathroom
而更大的信息是洗手间的信息，因为您需要了解
and the bigger message is the bathroom message because you need to know the
message because you need to know the bigger masses of 350 plus one we've seen
更大的质量350加上一个，我们已经看到这批产品消失了，当我们改变时就可以了
bigger masses of 350 plus one we've seen this batch away yes when we change okay
this batch away yes when we change okay [Applause]
[掌声]
确实是我们之前所做的，但是现在我们有了这个观测系统
this batch away yes when we change okay [Applause]
it's really that's what we did before but now we have this observation system
确实是我们之前所做的，但是现在我们有了这个观测系统
but now we have this observation system but literally this is the update
但是从字面上看，这是更新方程，这是针对
but literally this is the update equation this is a equation for the
equation this is a equation for the market
市场
在太太Ballew常数，这是您知道您还没有被保留的事实
equation this is a equation for the market
in mrs. Ballew constant and it is you know you're not still be remaining which
在太太Ballew常数，这是您知道您还没有被保留的事实
know you're not still be remaining which part are you expensive actually the the
一部分是您实际上是昂贵的，死亡的自动化
part are you expensive actually the the automation of the death with the
automation of the death with the junction tree if you missed a map of
联结树，如果您错过了与不相关的传播图
junction tree if you missed a map of propagation related to not to the
propagation related to not to the message beta but to this message gamma
消息beta，但对于此消息gamma和此消息大蒜，您知道什么
message beta but to this message gamma and this message garlic you know what
and this message garlic you know what the pH is the posterior of QT given long
给定从y 0到Y的长期关系，pH是QT的后验
the pH is the posterior of QT given long terms of relations from y 0 to Y
terms of relations from y 0 to Y tropical T so this map of messed again
热带T，所以这幅混乱的地图又是后部的
tropical T so this map of messed again is the posterior of should be given all
is the posterior of should be given all the observations of the capital T and
大写字母T的观察结果和你明天可以说妻子的消息
the observations of the capital T and you may say wife tomorrow message
you may say wife tomorrow message because if you do the calculations and
因为如果您进行计算并且它们很容易揭示唯一的给定
because if you do the calculations and they are simple to reveal the only gives
they are simple to reveal the only gives mister collation of the so to account
先生的整理，以便说明您有条件的独立性
mister collation of the so to account for some conditional independence you
for some conditional independence you can show that the gamma Q T to complete
可以显示伽马QT来完成您必须计算的每个Masters
can show that the gamma Q T to complete each you have to compute the Masters
each you have to compute the Masters gamma 3 T plus 1 and then months analyze
γ3 T加1，然后对KT加一学期进行数月分析
gamma 3 T plus 1 and then months analyze with respect to K T plus one semester
with respect to K T plus one semester and I want you to right now to worry
我希望您现在就可以担心有关问题的详细信息
and I want you to right now to worry about the details of the questions for
about the details of the questions for basically there is a data mess is
基本上有一个数据混乱正在向后传播，但也是
basically there is a data mess is propagating backwards but also is a
propagating backwards but also is a reminiscence
回忆一下，如果您喜欢有点不同，可以吗
reminiscence if you like what's a little different ok
if you like what's a little different ok they have different definitions okay and
他们有不同的定义好吗，如果知道硫磺质量，他们的日子也就好了
they have different definitions okay and their days if you know the sulfur masses
their days if you know the sulfur masses and the beta masters program a message
而beta大师有效地编写了一条消息，您可以计算出
and the beta masters program a message effectively you can calculate there is
effectively you can calculate there is nothing probability distribution of QT
没有给出所有数据的QT概率分布，所以如果您从不
nothing probability distribution of QT given all the data so if you never
given all the data so if you never observe esters you say give me a nice
观察您说的酯类，可以让我很好地预测要采取的状态
observe esters you say give me a nice smooth prediction of the state to take
smooth prediction of the state to take its effectively multiplying at least
它有效地使知识至少比营销更有效地传播
its effectively multiplying at least knowledge the further than the marketing
knowledge the further than the marketing message the same way with an unequal
通过不平等的培训以相同的方式传达信息记住我们需要的链条
message the same way with an unequal training remember for the chain we need
training remember for the chain we need to calculate the posterior several types
计算后几种常见措施的市场信息
to calculate the posterior several types of common measures the market message
of common measures the market message this is it do anything except to tell
除了告诉你这就是做任何事情
this is it do anything except to tell you
这个和另一个，我们将看到我们到达交点3的公式
this and the other and we will see the formulas we get to the junction 3 they
formulas we get to the junction 3 they are basically identical to the out
与您从中获得的out程序更新基本相同
are basically identical to the out program updates that you get with the
program updates that you get with the classical length we put using
我们把有条件的好的下一个作业放在经典长度上
classical length we put using conditional okay the next homework
conditional okay the next homework project so make it a comma because
项目，因此将其设为逗号，因为这就是为什么您可以了解有关
project so make it a comma because that's why you can learn something about
that's why you can learn something about data assimilation alright so so perfect
数据同化是如此完美